http://www.camerahouse.com.au/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
We have prepared this Privacy Policy to explain how we will handle the personal information of individuals who create a membership account and / or conduct online purchases from our website.
This web site is subject to the National Privacy Principles under the Australian Privacy Act 1988 (as amended by the Privacy Amendment (Private Sector) Act 2000) and This Privacy Policy explains in general terms how we protect the privacy of your personal information under the National Privacy Principles. It will apply to any personal information you provide to us when creating a membership account or transacting with us.
Application
We respect your privacy and are committed to protecting your personal information. We do not disclose confidential information about you except as required to provide our services, with your consent or as required or permitted by law.
Collection of Your Personal Information
Personal information about you is used strictly for limited purposes.  From time to time, we will collect information about you such as your name, server address, domain name, contact details, occupation, title, the date and time of your visit and the information downloaded concerning the matters on which you seek our services.  This information is collected when you give it to us directly, when you use our services or when you visit our website.
Use of Your Personal Information
The personal information we collect about you is primarily used for the purpose of processing your order and communicating effectively with you about:
Returns and exchange authorisations;
Order confirmation;
Sending you tax invoices;
Delivering the products you have purchased online;
Providing you with dispatch and tracking information with regard to your online order(s);
Providing you with pick up details and tracking information with regard to your store pick up order(s);
Sending you e-mail newsletters containing special offers;
Administering your account; and
Servicing our relationship with you.
You may also sign up to receive periodic e-mail newsletters letting you know of our latest specials.  If at any time you decide you do not want to receive or continue to receive additional information from us, please refer to the heading "Subscribing and Unsubscribing to our e-mail marketing List contained within these terms.
There is an option to subscribe to the e-mail newsletter as part of any online transaction you conduct with us.
If you do not wish to provide us with personal information, we may be unable to properly provide you with the products, services, information and/or warranties that you require.
Disclosure of Personal Information
We will not disclose or share your personal information with our business partners unless you give Camera House your specific permission to do so.  However, from time to time we may send you material from our business partners. If you choose to accept those promotional offers or provide your information to those third parties, that is your choice.
We may, however, use or disclose your personal information to third party organisations for purposes relating to the management of your membership account with us. Such organisations include:
Service providers who manage the services we are able to provide you with;
Mailing systems which facilitate delivery of the products you have purchased with us;
Live help service providers;
Maintenance and repair services;
Market research; and
Our professional advisers such as lawyers, accountants and auditors.
Please be assured that we require these organisations to observe strict confidentiality obligations with regard to your personal information and are also bound to adhere to the National Privacy Principles. These third party service providers are not permitted to use your personal information for their own marketing purposes.
Security
Other than described above, we will not use, sell or disclose your personal information without your consent.  We endeavour to take all reasonable steps to keep secure any information which we hold about you and to keep this information accurate and up to date.
We have robust systems and procedures in place to protect your privacy and your information is stored in secure servers. We are continually upgrading these systems and reviewing our procedures to ensure the highest standard of security is used to protect your personal information.
We use the eWAY Payment gateway for our online credit transactions. eWay is an authorised third party processor for all major Australian Banks and all transactions are performed under a 128 Bit SSL Certificate and encrypted for storage within eWAY's bank-grade data centre.
However, notwithstanding the highest standards of care that we take with security, we cannot be held responsible for events arising from unauthorised access to your personal information.
We may, from time to time, engage third party contractors to carry out work for us.  Third party contractors are prohibited from using collected personal information about you, except for the specific purpose for which that personal information has been supplied by us to the contractor.
